<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mind Tricks VR</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="text">congratulations you have meditated for 40 hours in past week.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">This information will not be sold or shared with a third party. This information will be used for sorting analytical data and sharing that information with the user. We will use this info to contact you about new releases and features and to help us investigate technical support requests. To delete this information please go to the feedback page and select the subject delete user info and then send.</string>


<string name="instructions">The purpose of meditation is not to clear your mind of all thoughts but to understand how your mind works. Once you understand, you’re no longer at its mercy. The purpose of the mantra “Love” is to focus on a word that does not represent a tangible object or have only one specific meaning.\n\n
Find a quiet, comfortable place to sit down. You may want to play some soft light music. First, take a normal breath. Then try a deep breath: Breathe in slowly through your nose, allowing your chest and lower belly to rise as you fill your lungs. Let your abdomen expand fully. Now breathe out slowly through your mouth (or your nose, if that feels more natural).\n\nOn the app, you can select the speed of the scrolling mantra. The minimum is 3 seconds and the maximum is 20. Let’s start with five.\n\nInhale for 5 seconds, then hold for 5 seconds, then exhale for 5 seconds, then hold for five seconds. Repeat. You can also combine cycles. For example, instead of 5 seconds you could select 10 seconds; inhale and hold for a combined 10 seconds then exhale and hold for a combined 10 seconds.\n\nThoughts are constantly arising in the mind and the goal of meditation is to not grasp on to these thoughts but to observe them and then let them go. Focus on the breath, using deep abdominal breathing. When thoughts arise you can acknowledge them, label them, let them go and then go back to the breath. You can make your own list of thought categories. Some examples would be planning mind, anxious mind, worrying mind, judging mind, etc. You may find it helpful to focus on the scrolling text first and as you progress, focus more on the breath while you passively observe the text.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
</resources>
